- Individual relish packets? Onion rings?
- Yes.
- Extra breading? What did they say?
- I asked. No.
- Did you protest? Vociferously?
- Yes. No.
(Sheldon:)Well, then, what took you so long?
(Leonard:)Just eat.
- Hey, guys. What'd I miss, what'd I miss?
- Giselle's hanging by a thread.
(Penny:)Oh, good, I hate her.
(Howard:)Then you're not invited to our wedding.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, do we have to suffer...
(Sheldon:)...through this transparently manipulative,
pseudo-reality again?
ALL:
Yes.
(Sheldon:)You and I have a standing TV schedule...
(Sheldon:)...the result of extensive debate
and compromise.
(Sheldon:)Any alterations
except for breaking news...
(Sheldon:)...have to be pre-approved
at the weekly roommate meeting.
(Leonard:)Put it on the agenda.
(Sheldon:)You have to make a motion.
(Leonard:)I'll make a motion
but you're not gonna like it.
(Sheldon:)Fine. Mock parliamentary procedure.
(Sheldon:)At least put it on mute.
(Penny:)Oh, Giselle's not getting kicked off.
It's totally gonna be Summer.
[SQUEALS]